// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
    answer: "Object-Based",
    options: [
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Object-Based",
      "Assembly-language",
      "High-level"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression",
    answer: "immediate if",
    options: [
      "Alternative to if-else",
      "Switch statement",
      "If-then-else statement",
      "immediate if"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The function and var are known as:",
    answer: "Declaration statements",
    options: [
      "Keywords",
      "Data types",
      "Declaration statements",
      "Prototypes"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not an error in JavaScript?",
    answer: "Division by zero",
    options: [
      "Missing of Bracket",
      "Division by zero",
      "Syntax error",
      "Missing of semicolons"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "CSS stands for",
    answer: "Cascading style sheets",
    options: [
      "Cascade style sheets",
      "Color and style sheets",
      "Cascading style sheets",
      "None of the above",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is",
    answer: "background-color",
    options: [
      "bgcolor",
      "color",
      "background-color",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following has introduced text, list, box, margin, border, color, and background properties?",
    answer: "CSS",
    options: [
      "HTML",
      "PHP",
       "CSS",
       "Ajax"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is",
    answer: "opacity",
    options: [
      "opacity",
      "filter",
      "visibility",
      "overlay"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of combinator?",
    answer: "*",
    options: [
      ">",
      "~",
      "+",
      "*"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following scoping type does JavaScript use",
    answer: "font-size",
    options: [
      "font-size",
      "text-size",
       "text",
       "size"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];